A Guide to the University Relations Clippings File of the Office of Information Services, 1969-1970
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
University Relations Clippings File of the Office of Information Services 1969-1970
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-4/2/8.701
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the university library on 1977 April 2.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of the Clippings File of the Office of Information Services.
Contents List
- Sesquicentennial--Charter Day Celebration Dinner 1969 (Box 1)
- Sesquicentennial--Newcomen Dinner 1969 Jan-Feb (Box 1)
- Sesquicentennial--Convocation (photograph contact sheets) 1969 (Box 1)
- Sesquicentennial--Counter-Convocation 1969 (Box 1)
- Sesquicentennial Convocation 1969 Oct (Box 1)
- Sesquicentennial--Correspondence 1967 Jan-1969 Dec (Box 1)
- Sesquicentennial--Correspondence with Charlottesville Daily Progress 1968 Dec-1969 Jun (Box 1)
- Sesquicentennial--Miscellaneous 1969 (Box 1)
- Sesquicentennial--Newspaper Clippings 1969 Feb-1970 Jan (Box 1)
- Sesquicentennial--Miscellaneous 1967 Apr-1969 Oct (Box 2)
- Sesquicentennial--Visiting Scholars and Special Programs 1969-1970 (Box 2)
- Sesquicentennial--Sesquicentennial Scholars 1969-1970 (Box 2)
- Sesquicentennial--Charlottesville Daily Progress Special Sesquicentennial Edition 1969 Apr 13 (Box 2)